https://www.beersofeurope.co.uk/privacy-policy

Basket
(0)
Basket
(0)
Basket
(0)
Crones
Ets Guillet Frères SA - Cidrerie Kerisac (Agrial)
Cognac
Cognac (Special Cuvee)
Cognac (VS)
Cognac (VSOP)
Cognac (XO & Napoleon)
Eau De Vie
Gin
Gin (Flavoured)
Gin (Plain)
Grappa
Jenever
Liqueur
Liqueur (Chocolate and Coffee)
Liqueur (Coffee)
Liqueur (Cream)
Liqueur (Fruit)
Liqueur (Fruits)
Liqueur (Herb)
Liqueur (Other)
Liqueur (Whiskey)
Mead
Pisco
Poteen
Rum
Rum (Dark)
Rum (Flavoured)
Rum (Golden)
Rum (Spiced)
Rum (White)
Tequila/Mezcal
Tequila/Mezcal (Anejo)
Tequila/Mezcal (Flavoured)
Tequila/Mezcal (Gold)
Tequila/Mezcal (Reposado)
Tequila/Mezcal (White)
Vermouth and Aperitifs
Vodka
Vodka (Flavoured)
Country
Argentina Australia Austria Bangladesh Barbados Belgium Brazil Canada Chile China Corsica Croatia Cuba Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Dominican Republic Estonia Ethiopia Fiji Finland France Germany Greece Guatemala Hungary Iceland India Ireland Italy Jamaica Japan Kenya Laos Latvia Lithuania Luxembourg Madeira Malta Mauritius Mexico Morocco Namibia Netherlands New Zealand Nigeria Norway Peru Poland Portugal Romania Russia Sardinia Singapore Slovakia Slovenia South Africa South Korea Spain Sri Lanka Sweden Switzerland Tanzania Thailand Trinidad and Tobago Turkey Uganda Ukraine United Kingdom USA Vietnam
Producer
Adnams All Others Anarchy Brew Co Anchor Brewery Augustiner Banks (Barbados) Breweries Ltd Barsham Brewery Beavertown Brewery Brewdog Brugse Zot Chimay Damm Grimbergen Guinness Herforder Hoegaarden Jever Leffe Lowenbrau Maisel Moon Gazer Moosehead Breweries Paulaner Saltaire Brewery Samuel Adams Samuel Smiths Stieglbrauerei zu Salzburg Trappistes Rochefort Westmalle
Style
Abbey Dubbel Abbey Tripel ABT/Quadrupel Alcopop Ales/Bitters Altbier Amber Ale Amber Lager/Vienna American Pale Ale American Strong Ale Baltic Porter Barley Wine Belgian Ale Belgian Strong Ale Belgian Style Ales Belgian White Berliner Weisse Biere de Garde Bitter Black IPA Bock Beers Brown Ale California Common Christmas Beer Cream Ale Czech Pilsner Doppelbock Dortmunder/Helles Dry Stout Dunkel/Schwarzbiers Dunkel/Tmavy Dunkelweizen Dunkler Bock Eisbock English Pale Ale English Strong Ale Foreign Stout Fruit Beer German Hefweizen German Kristalweizen Golden Ale/Blond Ale Grodziskie/Gose/Lichtenhainer Halloween Heller Bock Imperial Stout Imperial/Double IPA Imperial/Strong Porter India Pale Ale Irish Ale Kolsch Lager/Pils Lambic Style - Faro Lambic Style - Gueze Lambic Style - Unblended Low Alcohol Beers Malt Liquor Mead Mild Ale Oktoberfest/Marzen Old Ale Pale Ales Pale Lager Pilsener Polotmavy Porter Premium Bitter/ESB Premium Lager Radler/Shandy Saison Schwarzbier Scotch Ale Scottish Ale Smoked/Rauchbier Beers Sour Beers Sour Red/Brown Sour Wild Ale Speciality Grain Spice/Herb/Vegetable Stouts Strong Pale Lager/Imperial Pils Sweet Stout Traditional Ale Weizen Bock Wheat Ale Wheat Beers Zwickel/Keller/Landbier Zwickel/Keller/Lichtenhainer
Cider
Country
Australia Austria Estonia France German India Ireland Italy Latvia Lithuania New Zealand South Africa Spain Sweden United Kingdom USA
Producer
All Others Celtic Marches Beverages Ltd Crones Ets Guillet Frères SA - Cidrerie Kerisac (Agrial) Guillet Freres Company Healeys Cornish Cider Farm Herrljunga Cider AB Kopparberg Lilleys Cider Lyme Bay Winery Sheppy’s Cider The Garden Cider Co
Style
Cider Dry Cider Flavoured Ciders Medium Cider Perry/Pear Cider Sweet Cider
Wine
Country
Argentina Australia Austria Bulgaria Chile China Cyprus Estonia France Georgia Germany Greece Hungary India Italy Japan Latvia Lebanon Lithuania Madeira Moldova New Zealand Norway Poland Portugal Romania Russia Slovakia South Africa South Korea Spain Ukraine United Kingdom USA
Producer
All Others Berton Vineyards Pty Ltd Boutari Casella Wines Pty Limited Delgado Zuleta Jack Rabbit Keo Lindisfarne Ltd Lyme Bay Winery Reh Kendermann GmbH Weinkellerei Romate
Style
Dessert Wine Fortified Fruit Wine Red Wine Rose Wine Sparkling Wine White Wine
Spirits
Country
Antigua Armenia Australia Austria Azerbaijan Barbados Belgium Bermuda Bolivia Brazil British Virgin Islands British West Indies Bulgaria Canada Chile China Colombia Costa Rica Croatia Cuba Curacao Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Dominican Republic Estonia Fiji Finland France Germany Gran Canaria Greece Grenada Guatemala Guyana Haiti Honduras Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Ireland Italy Jamaica Japan La Réunion Latvia Lebanon Lithuania Madeira Martinique Mauritius Mexico Moldova Nepal Netherlands New Zealand Nicaragua Norway Panama Peru Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Romania Russia Serbia Seychelles Slovakia Slovenia South Africa South Korea Spain St Lucia St Vincent St. Kitts and Nevis Suriname Sweden Switzerland Tahiti Taiwan Tenerife Thailand Trinidad and Tobago Turkey Ukraine United Kingdom USA Venezuela Vietnam West Indies
Producer
All Others Asbach Berentzen Black Shuck Bols Braeckman Bullards Carolans De Kuyper Filliers Jack Daniels Keglevich Lubelska Monin The Dalmore Wild Knight Wyborowa Zymurgorium
Style
Absinthe Alcopop Aquavit Armagnac Baijiu Bitters Brandy Cachaca Calvados Cognac Cognac (Special Cuvee) Cognac (VS) Cognac (VSOP) Cognac (XO & Napoleon) Eau De Vie Gin Gin (Flavoured) Gin (Plain) Grappa Jenever Liqueur Liqueur (Chocolate and Coffee) Liqueur (Coffee) Liqueur (Cream) Liqueur (Fruit) Liqueur (Fruits) Liqueur (Herb) Liqueur (Other) Liqueur (Whiskey) Mead Pisco Poteen Rum Rum (Dark) Rum (Flavoured) Rum (Golden) Rum (Spiced) Rum (White) Schnapps Soju Specialist Speciality Syrups & Cordials Tequila/Mezcal Tequila/Mezcal (Anejo) Tequila/Mezcal (Flavoured) Tequila/Mezcal (Gold) Tequila/Mezcal (Reposado) Tequila/Mezcal (White) Vermouth and Aperitifs Vodka Vodka (Flavoured) Whisky
Glasses
Country
Albania Argentina Austria Belgium Bulgaria Canada China Corsica Cuba Czech Republic Denmark France Germany Greece India Ireland Italy Laos Mauritius Namibia Netherlands New Zealand Norway Poland Portugal Russia Singapore Slovenia South Korea Spain Sri Lanka Sweden Thailand Turkey United Kingdom USA
Glass Type
Boot Chalice Flute Goblet Pokal Shot/Cocktail Snifter Stange Tankard/Stein Tulip/Thistle Tumbler Weizen
Giftpacks
Country
Belgium France Germany Ireland Latvia Netherlands United Kingdom USA
Producer
All Others Brasserie d’Orval Chimay St. Peters Brewery Trappist Rochefort Westmalle
Mixed Cases
Home Brew
Beer Kits
Better Brew Black Rock Kits Brewferm Beer Kits Brewmaker Bulldog Beer Kits Coopers Beer Kits Edme Beer Kits Geordie Beer Kits Hambleton Bard John Bull Beer Kits Muntons Beer Kits St Peters Beer Kits Tiny Rebel Kits Tom Caxton Beer Kits Tooheys Beer Kits Woodfordes Beer Kits Youngs Beer Kits
Cider Kits Wine Kits
Merchandise
Trustpilot
PLEASE NOTE: Last Orders for Guaranteed shipping before Christmas is Midday Wednesday 19th December.
PLEASE NOTE: Last Orders for Guaranteed shipping before Christmas is Midday Wednesday 19th December.
Home
/
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY POLICY
Beers of Europe Ltd privacy policy 1. Background This privacy notice lets you know what happens to any personal data that you give to us, or any that we may collect from or about you. It applies to all products and services, and instances where we collect your personal data.
This privacy notice applies to personal information processed by or on behalf of Beers of Europe Ltd. By using this website you agree to our terms and conditions. Changes to this privacy notice We may change this privacy notice from time to time by updating this page to reflect changes in the law and/or our privacy practices. We are happy to supply you with a copy of any changes we make on request. 2. What kinds of personal information about you do we process? Personal information that we’ll process in connection with all our products and services, if relevant, includes: Personal and contact details, such as title, full name, contact details and contact details history
Records of your contact with us such as if you get in touch with us using our online services including Email, Amazon, or by telephone or in person.
Products and services you hold with us, as well as have been interested in, and have held (if deemed as a business need) and the associated payment methods used
The usage of our products and services, such as rental agreement details and invoices.
Information we obtained from third parties, including information about insurance risk, pricing, claims history, instances of suspect fraud and usage history
Financial details about you, such as your bank account for BACS payments. 3. What is the source of your personal information? We’ll only collect personal information from you or your business directly.  4. What do we use your personal data for? We use your personal data, including any of the personal data listed in section above, for the following purposes: Assessing an application for a product or service, such as rental of space or account requests.
For processing and delivering orders
Managing products and services relating to that the product or service, or application for one
Updating your records, paying you monies due, and recovering any payments due to us.
Managing any aspect of the product or service
To make automated decisions on whether to offer you a product or service, or the price, payment method, risk or terms of it
To perform and/or test the performance of, our products, services and internal processes
To improve the operation of our business.
To follow guidance and best practice under the change to rules of governmental and regulatory bodies
For management and auditing of our business operations including accounting
To monitor and to keep records of our communications with you and our staff
To administer our good governance requirements
For direct marketing communications and related profiling to help us to offer you relevant products and service, including deciding whether to offer you certain products and service. We’ll send marketing to you by email, phone, post, social media and digital channels (for example, using Facebook). Offers may relate to any of our products and services which we think may interest you.
To provide personalised content and services to you, such as tailoring our products and services, our digital customer experience and offerings, and deciding which offers or promotions to show you on our digital channels
To develop new products and services and to review and improve current products and services
To comply with legal and regulatory obligations, requirements and guidance
To provide insight and analysis of our customers both for ourselves and for the benefit of business partners either as part of providing products or services, helping us improve products or services, or to assess or improve the operating of our businesses
To facilitate the sale of one or more parts of our business
Should a purpose not be listed above, but deemed necessary, we will explain it at the time 5. What are the legal grounds for our processing of your personal information (including when we share it with others)? We rely on the following legal bases to use your personal data: 1. Where it is needed to provide you with our products or services, such as:
a) Assessing an application for a product or service you hold with us, including consider whether or not to offer you the product, the price, the payment methods available and the conditions to attach
b) Managing products and services you hold with us, or an application for one
c) Updating your records and contacting you about your account
2. Where it is in our legitimate interests to do so, such as:
a) Managing your products and services relating to that, updating your records,
b) To perform and/or test the performance of, our products, services and internal processes
c) To follow guidance and recommended best practice of government and regulatory bodies
d) For management and audit of our business operations including accounting
c) To carry out monitoring and to keep records of our communications with you and our staff
g) To administer our good governance requirements using Facebook
j) Subject to the appropriate controls, to provide insight and analysis of our customers to provide products or services, helping us improve products or services, or to assess or to comply with our legal obligations
With your consent or explicit consent:
a) For some direct marketing communications 6. When do we share your personal information with other organisations?
We will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise any information, except where you give your express consent to do so, to any third parties. We only share information with PayPal, Sagepay and Amazon for payment purposes. 7. How and when can you withdraw your consent?
Where we’re relying upon your consent to process personal data, you can withdraw this at any time by contacting us using the details below. 8. Is your personal information transferred outside the UK or the EEA?
We do not share your information outside the UK 9. What should you do if your personal information changes?
You should tell us so that we can update our records. 10. Do you have to provide your personal information to us?
We’re unable to provide you with our products or services if you do not provide certain information to us. In cases where providing some personal information is optional, we’ll make this clear. 11. Do we do any monitoring involving processing of your personal information?
In this section monitoring means any: listening to, recording of, viewing of, intercepting of, or taking and keeping records (as the case may be) of calls, email, text messages, social media messages, in person (face to face) meetings and other communications.
We may monitor where permitted by law and we’ll do this where the law requires it, or to comply with regulatory rules, to prevent or detect crime, in the interests of protecting the security of our communications systems and procedures and for quality control and staff training purposes. This information may be shared for the purposes described above. 12. Automated decision making
We only make automated decisions if we have tried to contact you for a quick decision and have been unable to do so. 13. For how long is your personal information retained by us?
Unless we explain otherwise to you, we’ll hold your personal information based on the following criteria:
For as long as we have reasonable business needs, such as managing our relationship with you and managing our operations
For as long as we provide goods and/or services to you and then for as long as someone could bring a claim against us; and/or
Retention periods in line with legal and regulatory requirements or guidance. 14. What are your rights under data protection laws?
Here is a list of the rights that all individuals have under data protection laws. They don’t apply in all circumstances. If you wish to use any of them, we’ll explain at that time if they are engaged or not. The right of data portability is only relevant from May 2018. The right to be informed about the processing of your personal information
The right to have your personal information corrected if it is inaccurate and to have incomplete personal information completed
The right to object to processing of your personal information
The right to restrict processing of your personal information
The right to have your personal information erased (the “right to be forgotten”)
The right to request access to your personal information and to obtain information about how we process it
The right to move, copy or transfer your personal information (“data portability”)
Rights in relation to automated decision making which has a legal effect or otherwise significantly affects you You have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office which enforces data protection laws: https://ico.org.uk/. You can contact us using the details below. 15. Your right to object
You have the right to object to certain purposes for processing, in particular to data processed for direct marketing purposes and to data processed for certain reasons based on our legitimate interests. You can contact us by going to the Contact Us section of our website to exercise these rights. 16. What are your marketing preferences and what do they mean?
We may use your home address, phone numbers, email address and social media or digital channels (for example, Facebook, Google and message facilities in other platforms) to contact you according to your marketing preferences. You can stop our marketing at any time by contacting us using the details below or by following the instructions in the communication.
Trustpilot
SIGN UP FOR OFFERS, LAUNCHES AND NEWS
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Thank You For Signing Up To Our Newsletter
×
We look forward to keeping you up to date on all our news, offers, new products and much much more!
Close
Check our social media
CONTACT US Tel: 01553 812000
Fax: 01553 813419
Email: sales@beersofeurope.co.uk
OPENING HOURS Mon - Sat 9am - 6pm
Sun & Bank Hols 10am - 4pm
ABOUT
Kings Lynn, Norfolk, PE33 0BE
Copyright © 2018 Beers of Europe Ltd. All Rights Reserved. Registered Office: Garage Lane | Setchey | King's Lynn | Norfolk | PE33 0BE | Company Number: 04101517 | VAT Number: 759978931
We use
cookies to ensure that you receive the best experience possible whilst you use our website
Accept
